if for example we built a society in which there is
если например мы построили Общество в
no state and its institution
котором нету государства и его института
We are armed everyone with a weapon Yes,
Мы вооружённый каждый с оружием Да вот у
I have a spear You have a spear I
меня есть копьё У вас есть копьё я
defend my house you defend yours Yes, uh,
защищаю свой дом вы защищаете свой Да
who and how will
ээ кто и как будет
resolve a property dispute For example, I
решать имущественные спор Например я
come and say that no, this house is due to
прихожу и говорю что нет этот дом
me and you say that it is due to
положен мне а вы говорите что положен
you and we start poking around with spears
вам и мы начинаем на копьях
Hello Hello Is this your
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Это у вас
chromakey or a real
хромакей или реальный
carpet a real chromakey I understand throw
ковёр реальный хромакей понял киньте
something in there let's see or is it Roque or Yes
туда что-то посмотрим или это Роке или
I have already thrown it and the World Cup conversations conversations what is the important
Да я уж кидал а ЧМ беседы бесед как важ
channel called throw it I wonder if
канал называется киньте мне интересно ли
this is the real Roque or Well, let's
это реальный Роке или Ну ну давайте
watch
смотреть
op here you are behind you Threw something on the
оп вот вы что-то сзади себя Кинули на
pillow here throw something on Green
подушку вот ту киньте что-то на Зелёную
on Green Well, let's go yeah okay Everything is
на Зелёную Ну давайте да окей Всё
real so that's what the conversation conversations fuss about What is
реально так вот о чём беседа бесед суете
your channel called Andrey
Как ваш канал канал называется Андрей
Popok by my first and last name And
попок по моему имени и фамилии А
yours I have several channels but Sandro
ваш у меня несколько каналов но Сандро
Sandro understood I communicate on the topic of politics
Сандро понял я общаюсь о теме политики
war  Wow, politics And what political party do you
войны Ничего себе по политике А вы какой
adhere to? I'm a conservative. What is this?
придерживайтесь я консерватор А что это
And who are you, an anarchist? Cool, yes,
такое А вы кто анархист Прикольно да
Kropotkin, some modern ones, no, no,
Кропоткине какие-то современные ти не не
well, the closest to me are Stirner and
ну мне ближе всего давайте так штирнер и
Samuel Edward Konkin, and of the modern
Самуэль Эдвард конкин т а из современных
Russian anarchists, who did you single out? Oh,
российских анархистов кого вы выделили О
yes, you think I know them. Well, rbov is good. Who is
да думаете их знаю Ну рбов хороший Кто
there?
там
In pre-revolutionary Russia, the
е в до революционной России очень сильно
anarchist movement was very strong and, in
было развито анархические движение и в
principle, anarchists were one of the
принципе анархисты были одний из
driving forces of the Revolution. You could say that
движущих сил Революции можно сказать да
they simply did not take shape as
просто они не так оформились в
political forces due to their specific
политические в силу своей специфики
ideology. Political forces did not take shape as political forces, like the
идеологии не так оформились политические
Bolsheviks of the era, and they did not become,
силы как те же большевики эры и не стали
say, an organized political
скажем организованной политической потом
force later. Yeah, but in terms of, let's say,
силой Угу но в плане скажем
counteraction. That's tsarism. Yes, it
противодействия Вот это царизму Да
was really despotism and
деспотии это было действительно и
anarchist ideas were very popular,
анархические идеи очень были популярны в
including in Ukraine, there was
том числе на территории Украины был
Nestor Makhno, free territories.
Нестор Махно вольные территори Ну
Of course. He also adhered to these.
конечно Он придерживался тоже вот этих
Well, I won't say that he was
Ну как не скажу что он был
really struck by these ideas. Well,
прям сильно поражён этими идеями Так ну
due to his own
вот в силу своего какого-то
understanding of anarchism.  he tried to
там понимания анархизма он Вот пытался
implement such and here's what do you
реализовывать такие а вот как вы
think about anarchism, there are anarchists
считаете анархизм вот есть анархисты
who don't perceive the state at all Yes,
которые вообще не воспринимают
that the state shouldn't
государство Да что государство не должно
exist And there are those who,
быть А есть те которые
as it were, say that the state seems to be
э как бы говорят что государство вроде
possible but in essence, uh, it
как и может быть но по сути ээ у него
should have a curtailed, not all functions, that's
должны быть урезанный не все функции вот
how you see it, the state should exist
как вы видите государство должно быть
or shouldn't
или не должно
exist, look, I have a
быть смотрите у меня на это что-то
somewhat extravagant opinion about this I
несколько экстравагантное мнение Я
think that anarchism is, first
считаю что анархизм - это это в первую
of all, not about the State at all, I
очередь вообще не про Государство это я
perceive anarchism as, well, if you like, a kind of
воспринимаю анархизм как ну если хотите
variety or
такой такая разновидность или
branch or something like that of
ответвление или как-то так
existentialism, that is, anarchism
экзистенциализма вот то есть анархизм -
is, first of all, about me, about
это в первую очередь про меня про
personality and not about some abstract
личность и не про какую-то абстрактную
personality, yes, about a specific me, about
личность да про конкретного меня про
you specifically, this is actually in style, as it
конкретно вас это собственно по штир как
were, here the thing is that look, any
бы вот тут дело в том что смотри любая
theory, let's say If we look at
теория она скажем Если мы смотрим
some philosophy Yes, we can
какую-то философию Да мы можем её
project it onto ourselves, but any
проектировать в себя но любая
political theory is projected onto
политическая теория она проецируется на
relationships in society
отношения в обществе
Yes, that's why we can't That is, how do you
Да поэтому мы не можем в То есть как вы
see interaction with other people
видите взаимодействие с другими людьми
Should there be a police? Should there be a police?  to be a
Должна ли быть полиция должно ли быть
state Yeah yeah
государство Угу угу
look I'll just clarify now about this
смотрите Я просто сейчас уточню по вот
first my sleep here I just
этому первом мою спи здесь я просто на
rely on what is close to me Why do I
что опираюсь ну что мне близко Почему я
say this and this is actually
вот так говорю а это вот собственно
Stirner Max Stirner A which he has
штирнер Макс штирнер А который у него
here e Most likely you know his book is the
вот е Скорее всего вы знаете его книга
only one and his property is
единственный и его собственность
called there you can
называется там можно предисловие
read the preface there is his short preface
прочитать там маленькое его предисловие
and there he beautifully
такое и там вот он прекрасно
aphoristic he describes my business -
афористические он расписывает моё дело -
This is not a matter of truth not a matter of God not a matter of the
Это не дело истины не дело Божье не дело
nation not a matter of good or evil my business is
нации не дело там добра или зла моё дело
- This is only my business then he
- Это только моё дело дальше он
describes about his Union of egoists yes yes
расписывает про свой Союз эгоистов да да
Okay I'm now Yes I got it I got it
Хорошо я сейчас Да я понял я понял
look about the interaction of people and
смотрите про взаимодействие людей а
here I don't have any specific
здесь у меня каких-то конкретных
views but the closest to me from what
воззрений нет но мне ближе всего из того
I know now is
что я сейчас знаю это агоризм
Konkin's third agorism here more specifically In what
Конкина третьего вот конкретнее В чём
without names what should a state be
без названий что вот должно государство
or not a
должно быть или нет армия
state army should be or not a
государственная должна быть или нет
police should be look if we are
полиция должна быть смотрите если мы
talking about a completely ideal for
говорим про совсем-совсем идеал
everyone an ideal then this is of course the Kingdom of God
всем идеал то это конечно Царствие Божие
which will come at the end of time or more
которое наступит в конце времён по
precisely after the end of time and in  there will
точнее после конца времён и в нём
naturally be no police,
естественно не будет никаких полиций
no states and nothing like that, just the
никаких государств и ничего подобного
kingdom of God Yes, the kingdom of God is
как раз царство Божье Да царство Божье -
not an anarchic concept,
это концепция не анархическая
it is a clear hierarchical system, there is
это чёткая иерархическая система есть
God As the highest, the highest Power, he has an
Бог Как высший высшая Сила есть у него
Angel And there are already these mortals
Ангел А есть уже вот эти смертные
who are there, they are just not anarchic,
которые там это как раз не анархические
well, Anarchy Yes, which of course
ну Анархия Да что само собой
implies the concept of being without power in
предполагает понятие это без власти по
essence, yes, without power, that is, and the Key
сути да без власти то есть и Ключевая
idea of ​​many, if not almost all,
идея многих если не почти всех
anarchist movements Yes, this is that
анархические течений Да это то что вот
once upon a time people lived conditionally without
когда-то люди жили условно без
states because the state
государств потому что государство
was formed at a certain
образовалось на определённом
historical stage, before, people lived there
историческом этапе раньше люди жили там
by tribal and other means, and that is what is now
родоплеменной и другими вот и что сейчас
possible in modern society, that
в современном обществе тоже можно что
the State is an apparatus of
вот Государство - это аппарат
violence that, say, oppresses a person
насилия который скажем угнетает человека
and is needed in order to build an
и нужно для того чтобы построить
ideal, abstract society Yes, we
идеальное там абстрактное общество Да
need to get rid of the state and its
нужно избавиться от государства и его
state
государственных
institutions, so the question is if, for example,
институтов так вот вопрос если например
we built a Society in which there is no
мы построили Общество в котором нету
state and its
государства и его
institutions, everyone has a weapon Yes,
институ нный каждый с оружием Да вот у
I have a spear You have a spear I am
меня есть копьё У вас есть копьё я
defending my home, you are defending yours Yes,
защищаю свой дом вы защищаете свой Да
who and how will
ээ кто и как будет
resolve property disputes  For example, I
решать имущественные споры Например я
come and say that no, this house is
прихожу и говорю что нет этот дом
supposed to be mine, and you say that it is supposed to be
положен мне а вы говорите что положен
yours, and we start poking around with spears, I
вам и мы начинаем на копьях тыкаться я
lose, I call the gang, my gang comes
проиграю зову братву приходит моя братва
with spears, and that's it, and so on, as a result, a
с копьями и всё и так в результате всё
state is born anyway,
равно рождается государство всё равно
some force is born that
рождается какая-то сила которая
establishes power and order. Uh-huh. Yes.
устанавливает власть и порядки У угу А
Before answering
да Позвольте перед тем как ответить на
your question, let me comment on
этот ваш вопрос про прокомментировать
your words about the kingdom of God, and
ваши слова о царствии божьем а здесь
look here. I believe that the power of God and the
смотрите Я считаю что власть Господа э и
divine hierarchy are absolutely not the
божественная иерархия - это абсолютно не
same as the power of man, and in
то же самое что власть человека и в
this regard, I highly recommend
связи с этим я очень рекомендую у
Berdyaev has a short article called
бердяева есть небольшая статья под
either Anarchy or Anarchism, I can't
то ли Анархия то ли анархизм сейчас не
remember now. Here. And there, at the end, are some wonderful
вспомню Вот И там в конце замечательные
words about the fact that a true hierarchy is a true
слова о том что подлинная иерархия - это
Anarchy, and a true
и есть подлинная Анархия а подлинная
Anarchy is a true hierarchy. He
Анархия - это есть подлинные иерархии он
cites Dante's rose, where there is a
приводит розу Данте где вот этот
hierarchy of petals in a rose, where each
иерархии лепестков в розе где каждый
petal is in its place, they make up a
лепесток на своём месте они составляют
true hierarchy, but it is not
подлинную иерархию но она не
pyramidal. So,  on the social
пирамидальная так вот по общественному
structure look these are all very
устройству смотрите это всё очень
good questions but for example if let's
хорошие вопросы но например если
say robar would have answered you as he
допустим робар бы вам ответил как он
wrote Let's look let's
писал Давайте смотрите давайте мы
do it this way
сделаем так
you avoid answering referring to quotes from
вы уходите от ответа ссылаясь на цитаты
different I don't need this Okay Ro I want
разных Мне это не нужно Ладно Ро Я хочу
you as a result Here you read
чтобы вы в результате Вот вы читали
Berdyaev read that as a result of your
бердяева читали того в результате своих
compilations you passed it through yourself
компиляции вы пропустили это через себя
filtered something out yes something as you see the
что-то отсеяли да что-то как вы видите
state Yes Oh life without
государство Да Ой жизнь без
states so No well this is a very general
государств так Не ну это очень общий
question you were talking about resolving
вопрос вы говорили про разрешение
property disputes Yes well this is one of the
имущественных споров Да ну вот один из
aspects one of the aspects Well look
аспектов один из аспектов Ну смотрите
this will happen in about the same way
это будет происходить примерно так же
as is happening now between
как сейчас происходит между
states Yes because among the
государствами Да потому что среди
states there is no main
государств нет какого-то главного
state that governs all the other
государства которое всеми остальными
states the state
государствами управляют государство
between themselves they have to somehow
между между собой им приходится как-то
negotiate specifically Specifically here I
договаривать конкретно Конкретно вот я
look I wanted I liked your
смотрите Я захотел мне понравилась ваша
wife Yes for example and your apartment and I
жена Да например и ваша квартира и я я
knock on your door in Vera I say so
стучусь к вам в Вере говорю значит
now this is my wife And my apartment So
теперь это моя жена И моя квартира Так
you blink your eyes in surprise yes Yeah How to
ты удивлённо хлопаешь глазами да Угу Как
resolve this dispute and after me
решить этот спор а за мной со мной
another 10 people of the lads come with me and say
приходит Ещё 10 человек братвы и говорят
Yes This  there will be his wife Well, let's say there is a
Да Это будет его жена Ну допустим есть
non-aggression agreement option yes when and
вариант договора о неагрессии да когда
this option is very well
причём этот вариант очень хорошо
combined with this very Bakunin
совмещается с этим самым с Бакунинской
idea agreement agreement non-aggression agreement yes who
иде договор договор о неагрессии да кто
will monitor the implementation of this
будет следить за исполнением этого
agreement Here we have all agreed We have
договора Вот мы все договорились Мы
accepted gathered at the community meeting we
приняли собрались на сборах общины мы
should not aggression towards each other the
должны не агрессировать друг на друга
UN statute was written Yes here is our community
статут ООН написали Да вот нашей общины
tomorrow I come with the gang I say I want
завтра Я прихожу с братвой говорю я хочу
his wife she is not beautiful everything I come and
его жену у не не красивый всё прихожу и
present you with a fact you say here is some
ставлю тебя перед фактом ты говоришь вот
kind of non-aggression agreement like And I am
есть типа договор о ненападении типа А я
you Yes I throw you out of the apartment the Criminal Code and
те Да выкидываю тебя из квартиры УК и
how should I solve all this I understood
как должен решать это всё я понял
look if we conclude an agreement on
смотрите если мы заключаем договор о
non-aggression accordingly I am
неагрессии соответственно меня
supported on the network and you become an
поддерживают в сеть и вы становитесь
enemy not only for me but also for all
врагом не только для меня но и Для всех
those
тех
who entered into this agreement on non-aggression
кто вступил в этот договор о неагрессии
For example, I don't really believe in some kind of
Например я не особо-то верю в какой-то
non-aggression agreement I am not a brainwasher there is also
там договор о неагрессии я не мозгова
in all of Russia the
есть ещё вот в вся Россия сделала
agreement on non-aggression was made Yes for example well
договор о неагрессии Да например ну
specifically in the city of Moscow in
конкретно в городе Москва в переулке там
such and such an alley I come to you in  nose who
таком-то я прихожу к вам в нос кто
should
должен меня
punish me Well, for example,
наказать Ну например
I you can't Because with me there are still
я вы не сможете Потому что со мной ещё
10 people of the lads Well, no matter how many of you there
братвы 10 человек ну вас сколько бы ни
are, there are ten of you of the lads There are
было у вас десятерых человек братвы вас
fewer of you than those who entered into the agreement
меньше чем тех кто вступил в договор
before aggression Now wait a second, wait
раней агрессии сейчас секундочку
a second, look, what about this
секундочку смотрите причём вот этот
agreement on non-aggression I am not
договор о неагрессии я не являюсь его
some kind of full or any kind of
там каким-то полным или каким-либо
supporter of it, just as an option Yes, here it is, it is
сторонником просто как вариант да вот он
very Ho, this is not a working system, it is not
он очень Хо это неработающая система это
I didn't finish Well,
не я же не договорил Ну
excuse me, it correlates very well and is
Простите он очень хорошо коррелирует и
compatible with the idea of ​​an anarchic federation
совмещается с идеей анархический федера
E again, yeah, in the fact that you are hiding behind
е снова уга в то что ты прячешься за
quotes,
цитатами
here we live now, imagine that
ва вот мы живём сейчас представь что не
neither Bakunins nor Berdyaevs exist, Ropo, here
существует ни бакуниных ни бердяева ропо
we are, living in the real world, like in this
вот мы жим в реальном мире как в этом
real
реальном
world, here's the solution
мире вот реша э
Continue So this agreement on non-
Продолжить Так вот это договор не
aggression correlates very well with the
агрессии очень хорошо коррелирует с
idea of ​​an anarchic Federation That is, this is
идеей анархический Федерации То есть это
management from the bottom up when there are
управление снизу вверх когда есть там
some, let's call it a word, communities or
некие назовём это словом общины или
municipalities or some other such
муниципалитеты или какие-то ещё такие
small entities that
небольшие образования которые внутри
know each other well within themselves, here  Well,
себя хорошо друг друга знают вот Ну
since they are part of one
поскольку они являются частью одного
society and by the way not a virtual
общества и кстати не виртуального
society like some kind of nation, yes, but
общества как нация какая-нибудь да вот а
quite real ones, which are familiar with each other
вполне реально которые Вот друг с другом
and they already elect some
знакомы и они уже выбирают от себя неких
delegates there to some general councils and so on and so on
делегатов там в какие-то общие советы и
and so on. That
так далее и так далее и так далее То
is, that is, they make social institutions,
есть то есть делают социальные институты
state ones, that is, they make deputies.
государственные то есть делают депутатов
Well, they elect a deputy, delegates the middle
Ну выбирают депутата делегирует сре
delegate. Yes, that's right, a deputy. What is a deputy, a
делегат Да правильно депутат Что такое
deputy, in translation, this is a
депутат депутат в переводе это и есть
delegate. Yeah. That is, this is the one to whom we
делегат Угу Вот то есть это тот кому мы
delegate our powers, yes, that is,
делегирую свои полномочия да то есть
we create some kind of
власти депутату мы создаём какой-то
state body for the deputy, the
государственный орган
veche, the
вече
Rada, the Duma, the Senate, the
рада Дума сенат Генеральные
States General, and it turns out to be a state. It then takes
штаты и получается государство оно
some kind of sheriff, conditionally, to implement its powers.
своих полномочий берёт какого-то шерифа
And so on and so on, and that's it. All the
условно И так дальше и всё и получается
same, the state builds up again.
Всё равно снова государство выстраивает
Sheriffs, as far as I know,
Шери шерифы насколько я знаю
were. Well, in my opinion, they were hired, if I'm not mistaken.
были Ну по-моему наняты если не ошибаюсь
Well, I can confuse things. Well, I'll say more than that. I don't
Ну могу путать Ну я больше того скажу Не
know how it is in Russia, in Ukraine, the
знаю как у вас в России у нас в Украине
police are also
полиция тоже
hired. They are hired and paid a
наняты их нанимают на работу и платят им
salary. No, I mean the local one.
зарплату Нет я имею в виду местный вот
This state.  the state hires a
этой государство государство нанимает
policeman Let me say
полицейского Позвольте сказать
some let's say thinkers distinguish between
некоторые скажем так мыслители различают
such concepts as a state and a
такие понятия как государство и
republic for example there is this Stop It's
республика например есть вот это Стоп
not some thinkers a republic and a
Это не некоторые мыслители республика и
monarchy are forms of state
монархия - это формы государственного
structure of
устройства
government I want to report to you an idea
правления хочу вот доложить вам мысль
look some thinkers
смотрите некоторые мыслители
I report distinguish Despite Here you
Докладываю различают Несмотря Вот вы
say that a republic is a form of
говорите что республика является формой
state structure And some
государственного устройства А некоторые
object yes So some
возражают
object to
да Значит некоторые возражают против
such an idea saying that these are almost
такой мысли говоря что это чуть ли не
opposite concepts well these are
противоположные понятия вот ну это
completely different forms It is impossible they
совершенно различные формы Нельзя они
say that it is impossible A republic cannot be called a
говорят что нельзя Республику называть
state and a state
государством и государство нельзя
cannot be called a republic This is a question of terminology I agree here But look and for example I basically like what some say in particular Moscow republicans I listened to one Belkovich I think his name is if I remember wrong in principle I like what he says
импонирует то что он говорит может быть
maybe I didn't really delve into it much maybe I don't know something but in
погружался может что-то не знаю но в
principle I like what he
принципе мне импонирует то что он
says and what and how he describes the
говорит и то что и то как он описывает
Republic in principle quite close
Республику в принципе достаточно близко
anarchists Look I asked you a
анархические Смотри я тебя спросил
specific question and you tell me
конкретный вопрос а ты мне говоришь
look Kropotkin look confederation look look
смотри Кропоткин смотри конфедерация
Bekovich look look look I do
смотри бекович смотри смотри смотри мне
n't need that you don't
не нужно о том что ты вам так не
like the last name so much okay because
нравится фамилии ну ладно потому что
look you're running away you say look I
смотри ты убегаешь ты говоришь вот я
listened to that one he has nice ideas I don't
слушал того у него красивые идеи Мне не
need any way I didn't listen to anyone just
нуж кае лад никого не слушал просто
just a republic come on like a
просто республика давай так как
republican like Belko HIV Like your
республиканец как белко ВИЧ Как твой
Berdyaev like everything like they want to solve
бердяев как всё как они хотят решить вот
this issue that I come with the gang there are
этот вопрос что я с братвой
10 of us yes Armed and
прихожу нас 10 человек да Вооружённых и
we give
мы даём
Well the device is
Ну устройство
direct direct direct democratic
прямой пря прямым демократическим
device there I don't know like in
устройством там я не знаю как в
some Athena roughly speaking for
какой-нибудь там Афина грубо говоря
example probably somewhere like that you
например наверное где-то так это ж вы уж
Belkovich Look again again
белькович Посмотрите ещё раз ещё раз
What direct direct democracy That is in
Какое прямое прямую демократию То есть в
Moscow yes should All Moscow gather for a
Москве да должна Вся Москва собраться на
meeting and vote or give you
веч и проголосовать или отдать вам
this apartment No municipality by municipalities
эту Нет муниципаль по муниципалитетам
let's say Well Moscow is a
допустим Ну вот Москва - это
municipality many
муниципалитет много
municipalities well into districts it is
муниципалитетов хорошо на районы оно
divided here is the Bolshoi district there in the south there
разделено вот район Большой там юга там
what are they called Okay that is this whole
как они называются Окей то есть вся эта
community should come down half a million Yes and
община должна сойти полумиллиона Да и
decide or give you an apartment No there
решить или отдать вам квартиру Нет там
less than Well I don't know how here in terms of
меньше чем Ну не знаю как бы здесь по
numbers I can't say but in
численности уже не скажу но в
principle well by the device as if
принципе ну устройством как бы
republican for example for example
республиканским к примеру например
republican or I repeat by the agreement to
республиканским или повторюсь договором
those who entered into it respectively
тем кто вступил в него соответственно
So I ask you And what is
Так я спрашиваю вас А что такое
conservatism yet Look you are running away from
консерватизм ещ Смотри ты убегаешь от
the very thing that I am running away Everything ran away everything ran away
самого шо убегаю Всё убежал убежал Всё
I am telling you again Look
убежал я же говорю я ещё раз Смотри
existentialist to me I don't want you to
экзистенциалист мне я не хочу чтобы ты
hide behind the term I want to understand how here I am
прятался за термин Я хочу понять как вот
look I am a
я смотри я
student You are a teacher Tell me a student chu
ученик Ты учитель Скажи мне ученику чу
No I understand No I have an answer to this question
Нет я понял Нет у меня на этот вопрос
What is conservatism I want to become an
Что такое консерватизм Я хочу стать
anarchist I want to become an anarchist Yes
анархистом я хочу стать анархистом Да
so I want to squeeze your ideas so but I do
так я хочу зажать твоими идеями так но я
n't understand who will protect me for
не понимаю кто меня будет защищать
example from an armed gang Well private
например от вооружённое банды Ну частной
police let's say for example sheriffs So
полиции допустим например шерифы Так
stop private police she can that is
стоп частная полиция она может то есть
So she works for that People's community
Так она работает на то Народная община
People's community Vigilantes I don't know  a
Народная община Дружинники Я не знаю
bunch of options Well, these are all state institutions Militia militia What was it
куча вариантов Ну это это всё институты
People's militia Yes, it was armed, it was
была Народная милиция Да вооружённая оно
renamed in the Soviet Union, well, they
ж в Советском Союзе его переименовали ну
made it militia That is, it is armed Everything is
сделали милиция То есть это вооружён всё
correct
верно
Good Once again, who will be who will be Yes,
хорошо Ещё раз кто будет кто будет
who will support this militia
Да вот эту содержать эту милицию кто
or will
будет смотреть за тем или
it
она
sign a subscription system like on Netflix
подпи подписочный системы как на netflix
Let's talk
Давайте поговорим
about What kind of
про Какая
subscription is not what kind of
подписочка не какая
subscription like this family doctor
подписочку как вот семейный этот доктор
I say to the family policeman Yes, and he
Я говорю семейному полицейскому Да и он
solves my problems Yes, of course, good so that
решает мои проблемы Да конечно хоро так
is, I understand correctly if I pay
то есть я правильно понимаю если я плачу
this policeman he will not initiate anything against me
этому полицейскому против меня он ничего
no that is, it turns out that this is
возбуждать нет то есть получается это
my personal policeman
мой личный полицейский будет
who will not watch over
который будет не смотреть за
law and order And work for me
правопорядком А работать на меня
specifically because I pay him No,
конкретно потому что я ему плачу Нет он
he will work for
он будет работать на
those in that is, there is more than one person there who
тех в то есть там там же не один человек
pays there are some communities there
платит там есть некоторые там сообщества
some Well, for example, there is in Moscow so that And in
некоторое Ну вот например есть в Моск
order to resolve disputes within
чтобы А чтобы разрешать споры внутри
themselves, they resort to court there their That's
себя они прибегает там к суду сво Вот
super super yes, for example, in Moscow
супер супер да вот например на Москве
it's like Different there are different ethnic
это как Разно там разные этнические
diasporas Yes at  Chechens have their own brotherhood
диаспоры Да у чеченцев своя братва
that decides according to their own concepts, Armenians have their
которая решает по своим понятиям у армян
own brotherhood, Azerbaijanis have their own brotherhood,
своя братва у азербайджанцев своя братва
Russians simply don't have a brotherhood. In short, there are all of them, in
русские без братвы просто Короче их все
short, there you are. How can you resolve a dispute between these brothers
короче там ти Да как между этой братвой
by agreement, not aggression
спор договором не агрессии
on Instagram? I don't know why this is what you're
на й Instagram Я не знаю для чого це то
looking at the office for, and for
для чого тоб там дивитись на офес а для
you, one, two, or three clicks. But you try
тебе оди два або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I'll be a CTA in me. There are a bunch of fouls there,
мене и я буду КТА в мене там Купа фолов
and I'll do a cool job, but a
и в мене буде класный найб робити но
cool video letter on Y and Popik Andriy.
крут видео пись на й и Попик Андрий
So let me wait for you.
Так давай я тебя чекаю